The preprocessing function is a function where we transform the input data.
前処理関数は入力データを変換する関数です
In beam, it's called as part of the analyze and transform dataset.
Beamではデータセット分析/変換の 一部としてこの関数を呼び出します
In TensorFlow, the things you do in preprocess will
TensorFlowの前処理で実行する内容は
get called essentially as part of the serving input function in TensorFlow.
処理入力関数の一部として呼び出されます
In other words, it will get added to the TensorFlow graph,
つまりTensorFlowグラフに追加され
and it could be executed in TensorFlow during serving.
処理中にTensorFlowで実行できます
Because it'll be executed as part of the TensorFlow graph,
TensorFlowグラフの一部として 実行されるため
the preprocessing function is restricted to functions that you can call from TensorFlow.
前処理関数は TensorFlowで呼び出せるものに限られます
You cannot call regular Python functions
通常のPython関数は呼び出せません
since the preprocess is part of the TensorFlow graph during serving.
前処理は TensorFlowグラフの一部であるためです
Let's look at an example.
例を見てみましょう
In this example, I'm taking a set of inputs and preprocessing them.
この例では一連の入力を前処理します
What is the data type of inputs?
入力のデータ型は何でしょうか
It's a dictionary whose values are tensors.
テンソル値のディクショナリです
Remember, this is what is returned from
これは処理入力関数からの戻り値であり
Input functions return features,
入力関数は特徴を返します
labels and thus, is a features.
さらにラベルも返されます
And features is a dict, a dictionary.
特徴はdict（ディクショナリ）です
TF transform will take care of converting the data that comes
分析フェーズ中にTF変換が実行され
in via P transform into tensors during the analysis phase.
P変換からのデータをテンソルに変換します
We take the tensors and we use them to
そのテンソルを使用して特徴を作成し
The first result, fare amount in my example,
この例の最初の結果は
is passed through unchanged.
変更なしで渡します
We take the input tensor and add it to the result, no changes.
入力テンソルも変更なしで結果に追加します
The next result we want is a day of the week.
次に曜日が必要です
We want this to be an integer.
整数として必要です
However, in the input,
ただし入力は
it is the string like Thu for Thursday.
Thu（木曜）のような文字列です
So what we are doing is that we're asking TensorFlow
そこでTensorFlow変換を利用して
What TF transform will do is to compute
トレーニングデータセット内の すべての曜日について
the vocabulary of all the possible days of the week in the training data set.
TF変換によりボキャブラリを計算します
It will do this during the analyze phase and use
これは分析フェーズ中に実行され
that information to do the string to int mapping in the prediction phase.
その情報を基に予測フェーズで 文字列を整数にマッピングします
Next, we want to scale off the drop flat into a number that lies between zero and one.
次はドロップフラットを 0から1の範囲にスケーリングします
In the analysis phase,
分析フェーズで
TF transform will compute the Min and the Max of the column,
TF変換が列の最小値と最大値を計算し
and use those values to scale the inputs.
その値を基に入力をスケーリングします
We can also invoke other TensorFlow functions.
別のTensorFlow関数も呼び出せます
In this case, I'm taking the input number of passengers,
ここではJSONの整数である乗客数を 実数値にキャストします
Once all the features have been created and added,
すべての特徴を作成/追加したら
we can return the result.
結果を戻します
The analyze and transform P transform happens on the training dataset.
分析と変換のP変換は トレーニングデータセットが対象です
What should happen on the evaluation dataset?
評価データセットはどうなるのでしょうか
For the evaluation dataset,
評価データセットについては
we carry a pretty much the same beam pipeline that we did on the training dataset.
トレーニングデータセットとほぼ同じ Beamパイプラインを実行します
There's one big exception though,
1つ大きな違いがあります
we don't analyze the evaluation dataset.
評価データセットの分析は行いません
If we are scaling the values,
値をスケーリングする場合
the values in the evaluation dataset will be
評価データセット内の値は
scaled based on the Min and Max found in the training dataset.
トレーニングデータセットの最小値/最大値を 基にスケーリングされます
So on the evaluation dataset,
評価データセットでは
we don't call analyze and transform,
分析と変換を呼び出さず
we just call transform data set.
TransformDatasetのみを呼び出します
This will take care of calling all the things that we did in preprocess, pretty cool?
これで前処理の内容がすべて自動的に 呼び出されます
Notice however, that the transform dataset needs as
ただしTransformDatasetの入力として
input that transform function that was computed on the training data.
トレーニングデータセットで計算した 変換関数が必要です
That's what makes the magic possible.
この部分が肝になります
Once we have the transform dataset,
TransformDatasetさえあれば
we can write it out just like we wrote out the training dataset.
トレーニングデータセットの場合と同じように 評価データセットを書き出せます